{\fad(1000,0)\shad0\bord0\p1\fscx15\fscy15)\clip(13.333,14.667,192,89.333)\move(102.4,201.2,102.4,137.2)}m 0 0 l 0 0 l 282 -337 l 469 -181 l 616 -357 l 1018 -21 l 982 23 l 623 -276 l 513 -145 l 668 -16 l 632 28 l 290 -257 l 43 37 l 43 37 l 0 0 m 306 -165 l 306 -165 l 332 -110 l 392 -101 l 349 -58 l 358 1 l 304 -27 l 250 1 l 260 -60 l 218 -102 l 278 -111 l 306 -165
m 0 0 l 0 0 l 282 -337 l 469 -181 l 616 -357 l 1018 -21 l 982 23 l 623 -276 l 513 -145 l 668 -16 l 632 28 l 290 -257 l 43 37 l 43 37 l 0 0 m 306 -165 l 306 -165 l 332 -110 l 392 -101 l 349 -58 l 358 1 l 304 -27 l 250 1 l 260 -60 l 218 -102 l 278 -111 l 306 -165
{\fsp5\shad0\bord0\fnPing Hei\b1\fs25\clip(28.8,87.657,177.829,117.143)\move(103.333,90.946,103.333,109.232)}SSK字幕组
SSK字幕组
{\fad(1000,0)\shad0\bord0\p1\fscx15\fscy15)\clip(13.333,14.667,192,89.333)\move(102.4,201.2,102.4,137.2)}m 0 0 l 0 0 l 282 -337 l 469 -181 l 616 -357 l 1018 -21 l 982 23 l 623 -276 l 513 -145 l 668 -16 l 632 28 l 290 -257 l 43 37 l 43 37 l 0 0 m 306 -165 l 306 -165 l 332 -110 l 392 -101 l 349 -58 l 358 1 l 304 -27 l 250 1 l 260 -60 l 218 -102 l 278 -111 l 306 -165
m 0 0 l 0 0 l 282 -337 l 469 -181 l 616 -357 l 1018 -21 l 982 23 l 623 -276 l 513 -145 l 668 -16 l 632 28 l 290 -257 l 43 37 l 43 37 l 0 0 m 306 -165 l 306 -165 l 332 -110 l 392 -101 l 349 -58 l 358 1 l 304 -27 l 250 1 l 260 -60 l 218 -102 l 278 -111 l 306 -165
{\fsp5\shad0\bord0\fnPing Hei\b1\fs25\clip(28.8,87.657,177.829,117.143)\move(103.333,90.946,103.333,109.232)}SSK字幕组
SSK字幕组
{\fad(1000,0)\shad0\bord0\p1\fscx15\fscy15)\clip(13.333,14.667,192,89.333)\move(102.4,201.2,102.4,137.2)}m 0 0 l 0 0 l 282 -337 l 469 -181 l 616 -357 l 1018 -21 l 982 23 l 623 -276 l 513 -145 l 668 -16 l 632 28 l 290 -257 l 43 37 l 43 37 l 0 0 m 306 -165 l 306 -165 l 332 -110 l 392 -101 l 349 -58 l 358 1 l 304 -27 l 250 1 l 260 -60 l 218 -102 l 278 -111 l 306 -165
m 0 0 l 0 0 l 282 -337 l 469 -181 l 616 -357 l 1018 -21 l 982 23 l 623 -276 l 513 -145 l 668 -16 l 632 28 l 290 -257 l 43 37 l 43 37 l 0 0 m 306 -165 l 306 -165 l 332 -110 l 392 -101 l 349 -58 l 358 1 l 304 -27 l 250 1 l 260 -60 l 218 -102 l 278 -111 l 306 -165
{\fsp5\shad0\bord0\fnPing Hei\b1\fs25\clip(28.8,87.657,177.829,117.143)\move(103.333,90.946,103.333,109.232)}SSK字幕组
SSK字幕组
翻译  娄小胖
翻译  Jophy
翻译  鸡腿
翻译  Regina
翻译  君故
翻译  小鱼干
校对  坑
校对  XY
校对  娄小胖
特效  一只蠢喵
压制  Hhjie
总监  一只蠢喵
复仇者联盟
{\c&H2D2F2C&\fs90\fn方正兰亭粗黑简体\b0\pos(640,373.6)\fad(1500,1000)\bord2\3c&H717775&\shad6\4c&H070623&}复仇者联盟{\pos(944,572)\clip(400,70,560,600)\t(500,10000,\clip(1900,50,1900,600))\c&H949998&}
无 限 战 争
无 限 战 争{\pos(944,572)\clip(300,70,560,600)\t(500,15000,\clip(1900,50,1900,600))\c&H24272B&}
斯蒂文
罗杰斯
{\fs13\c&HCDA479&\b1\fn方正兰亭粗黑简体\bord0\frz335.9\move(696.555,152.291,718.359,163.758,44,441)}斯蒂文
斯蒂文
罗杰斯
斯蒂文·罗杰斯
太 空
苏格兰
{\fn微软雅黑\b1\fs16.5\blur0.4\c&H9DA4B2&\frz0.9327\move(747,285,648.444,279.556,21,3155)}即时要闻
{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\blur0.3\c&H8E92B7&\frz0.9327\b1\move(793.666,303.667,736,300.333,28,2405)}纽约遭受袭击
{\fn微软雅黑\b1\fs19.5\blur0.4\c&HAEABB3&\frz0.9327\move(521.667,353.001,511.111,363.556,29,1155)}特别报道
{\fn微软雅黑\b1\fs19.5\blur0.4\c&HAEABB3&\frz0.9327\move(512.334,365.001,508.444,370.223,27,1904)}特别报道
{\fn微软雅黑\b1\fs24\blur0.4\c&H7C7493&\frz0.9327\move(625.667,375.668,617.777,386.223,29,1155)}托尼·史塔克失踪
{\fn微软雅黑\b1\fs24\blur0.4\c&H7C7493&\frz0.9327\move(623,387.668,617.777,394.223,27,1862)}托尼·史塔克失踪
虚无知地
奶昔大哥：麦当劳人物，紫色玩偶；类比国内“紫薯精”叫法。
瓦坎达
{\fn方正宋黑简体\blur0.4\c&HDDE3E2&\fs90\b1\fscx100\fscy96\fad(3000,3000)\pos(640,290.933)}尼德威阿尔
{\fn方正宋黑简体\blur0.4\c&HDDE3E2&\fs90\b1\fscx100\fscy96\fad(1500,0)\shad2\pos(640,252.533)\4c&H23252E&}泰坦星
《浑身是劲》：1984年上映的美国剧情电影
飞侠哥顿：1980年美国动作科幻电影中的人物
沃米尔星
发送中
这里是阿斯加德
This is the Asgardian
政治家号难民船
refugee vessel Statesman.
我们遭遇攻击
We are under assault.
重复 我们遭遇攻击
I repeat, we are under assault.
引擎失灵 救生系统损坏
The engines are dead, life support failing.
请求附近战船营救
Requesting aid from any vessel within range.
我们距离阿斯加德22个跳跃点
We are 22 jump points out of Asgard.
我们的船员均是阿斯加德的家庭成员
Our crew is made up of Asgardian families.
只有少数的战士
We have very few soldiers here.
我们不是军用飞船
This is not a warcraft.
重复 我们不是军用飞船
I repeat, this is not a warcraft.
仔细听我说
Hear me and rejoice.
被伟大的泰坦神所拯救
You have had the privilege
是你们莫大的荣幸
of being saved by the Great Titan.
或许你们认为这是受难
You may think this is suffering.
不
No.
这是救赎
It is salvation.
正是因为你们的牺牲
Universal scales tip toward balance
宇宙才趋于平衡
because of your sacrifice.
微笑吧
Smile.
因为即使告别尘世
For even in death,
你们也是灭霸的子民
you have become Children of Thanos.
我知道失败的滋味
I know what it's like to lose.
明知自己没有错 却还是失败了
To feel so desperately that you're right...
这种绝望的感觉
yet to fail, nonetheless.
很可怕
It's frightening.
让人不寒而栗
Turns the legs to jelly.
但我想问问你 结局会如何
But I ask you, to what end?
畏惧还是逃避
Dread it, run from it...
命运终会降临
destiny arrives all the same.
而现在 它已在眼前
And now, it's here.
或者我应该说
Or should I say...
我已在你面前
I am.
你废话太多了
You talk too much.
超能立方
The Tesseract.
还是你哥哥的人头
Or your brother's head.
我相信你已经选好了
I assume you have a preference.
噢 当然了
Oh, I do.
想杀就杀吧
Kill away.
够了 住手
All right, stop!
我们没有超能立方
We don't have the Tesseract.
它已经在阿斯加德被毁掉了
It was destroyed on Asgard.
你真是史上最差劲的弟弟
You really are the worst brother.
我向你保证 哥哥
I assure you, brother...
太阳会再次照耀我们
the sun will shine on us again.
你过于乐观了 阿斯加德人
Your optimism is misplaced, Asgardian.
我要声明一点 我不是阿斯加德人
Well, for one thing, I'm not Asgardian.
还有一点呢
And for another...
我们有浩克
we have a Hulk.
让他玩
Let him have his fun.
天父啊
Allfathers...
让黑魔法再一次流经我的
let the dark magic flow through me one last...
身体吧
time.
你这就不对了
That was a mistake.
不
No!
你要为此偿命
You're going to die for that.
嘘
Shh.
我谦虚的个体
My humble personage...
在您的伟大前鞠躬
bows before your grandeur.
任何人都不曾享有
No other being has ever had the might...
使用哪怕一颗无限原石的尊崇
nay, the nobility...
更不用说两颗了
to wield not one, but two Infinity Stones.
宇宙臣服于您的掌下
The universe lies within your grasp.
地球上还有两颗原石
There are two more stones on Earth.
我的孩子们啊 去找到它们 给我带回泰坦星
Find them, my children, and bring them to me on Titan.
父亲 我们不会让您失望的
Father, we will not fail you.
请容我打断一下
If I might interject.
如果要去地球 或许你们需要一位导游
If you're going to Earth, you might want a guide.
我确实在那片舞台上有过演出经历
I do have a bit of experience in that arena.
你说的是失败的经历吗
If you consider failure experience.
我说的是实战经历
I consider experience experience.
全能的神灭霸啊
Almighty Thanos...
我 洛基 阿斯加德的王子
I, Loki, prince of Asgard...
奥丁之子
Odinson...
约顿海姆的合法继承人
the rightful king of Jotunheim...
恶作剧之神
god of mischief...
在此向您献上
do hereby pledge to you...
我永生的忠诚
my undying fidelity.
永生
Undying?
你应该谨慎措辞
You should choose your words more carefully.
你
You...
永远不可能成为
will never be...
神
a god.
不
No!
这次你可没有复活的机会了
No resurrections this time.
不 洛基
No. Loki.
讲真 你一分钱都没有吗
Seriously, you don't have any money?
迷恋物质意味着精神空虚
Attachment to the material is detachment from the spiritual.
我会转告便利店小哥的
I'll tell the guys at the deli.
他们会给你做一个抽象的黑麦火腿三明治
Maybe they'll make you a metaphysical ham on rye.
噢 等等 我好像有200块钱
Oh. Wait, wait, wait. I think I have 200.
美元吗
Dollars?
-卢比 -换算后呢
- Rupees. - Which is?
呃 一块五
Uh, buck and a half.
就一块五你还想吃什么
What do you want?
我想吃金枪鱼三明治哎
I wouldn't say no to a tuna melt.
灭霸来了
Thanos is coming.
他来了
He's coming.
你说谁
Who?
慢点 慢点 我一字一句地跟你说清楚
Slow down, slow down. I'll spell it out for you.
你就是在胡言乱语
You're totally rambling.
-不 我没有 -你把我说糊涂了
- No, I'm not. - You lost me.
听着 就是你有没有做过一种梦
Look, you know how you're having a dream,
梦里你急着想要尿尿
and in the dream you gotta pee.
-继续 -好
- Yeah. - Okay.
然后你就会想 "我的天呐
And then you're like, "Oh, my God.
没有卫生间 我要怎么办啊"
"There's no bathrooms. What am I gonna do?
-"哦 有人在看着呢" -是哦
- "Oh, someone's watching." - Right.
"我要尿裤子了"
"Oh, I'm gonna go in my pants."
然后你从梦中醒来
And then you wake up and in real life
确实想要尿尿
you actually have to pee.
-没错 -有过这样的梦
- Yes. - Yeah.
-嗯 -谁都做过这样的梦
- Okay. - Everybody has that.
没错 这就是我要说的
Right, that's the point I'm trying to make.
恰恰就是昨晚 我梦见我们有了孩子
Apropos of that, last night I dreamt we had a kid.
感觉太真实了
It was so real.
我们用你怪叔叔的名字给他取名
We named him after your eccentric uncle.
呃 他叫什么来着
Uh, what was his name?
-哎 -摩根 对
- Right. - Morgan! Morgan.
-所以你一觉醒来 -自然醒
- So you woke up... - Naturally.
觉得我们应该
...and thought that we were...
-生个孩子 -好吧
- Expecting. - Yeah.
-可以吗 -不
- Yes? - No.
我做了这个梦 那么真实
I had a dream about it. It was so real.
如果你真的想要孩子
If you wanted to have a kid...
就不会天天戴着这个了
you wouldn't have done that.
既然你提起来了 我可以跟你说 这没什么
I'm glad you brought this up, 'cause it's nothing.
只是个放纳米颗粒的东西罢了
It's just a housing unit for nanoparticles.
你这么说可一点帮助都没有 好吗
You're not helping your case, okay?
不 这是可以拆掉的 这不是
No, this is detachable. It's not a...
你不需要这个
You don't need that.
我知道 我做过手术了
I know, I had the surgery.
我只是想保护你我
I'm just trying to protect us...
和未来的一家三口 仅此而已
and future usses and that's it.
万一衣柜里面有个怪物呢
Just in case there's a monster in the closet.
-而不是 你懂的 -正常的衣服
- Instead of, you know... - Shirts.
你真的太了解我了
You know me so well.
-天呐 -你把我要说的话都说了
- God. - You finish all my sentences.
你的衣柜里应该挂满正常的衣服
You should have shirts in your closet.
是呀
Yeah.
你知道还差什么吗 不再有意外
You know what there should be? No more surprises.
我们今晚要共进晚餐
We're gonna have a nice dinner tonight.
去炫耀一下这枚海瑞温斯顿的钻戒
Show off this Harry Winston.
对吧 我们不要再经历任何意外了 永远不要
Right? And we should have no more surprises. Ever.
我应该向你保证
I should promise you.
-是的 -我会的
- Yes. - I will.
谢谢你
Thank you.
托尼·史塔克
Tony Stark.
我是斯蒂芬·斯特兰奇博士 你得跟我走一趟
I'm Doctor Stephen Strange. I need you to come with me.
噢 对了 顺便祝你们新婚快乐
Oh, uh, congratulations on the wedding, by the way.
不好意思 我给你发过请帖吗
I'm sorry, you giving out tickets to something?
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
毫不夸张地说
It's not overselling it to say that
宇宙的命运现在悬于一线
the fate of the universe is at stake.
"我们"是谁
And who's "We"?
嘿 托尼
Hey, Tony.
布鲁斯
Bruce.
-佩珀 -嗨
- Pepper. - Hi.
-噢 -你还好吗
- Oh. - You okay?
在宇宙形成之初
At the dawn of the universe,
世界一片混沌 之后
there was nothing. Then...
嘭
Boom.
宇宙大爆炸形成了六颗元素水晶
The Big Bang sent six elemental crystals...
划过原始的宇宙
hurtling across the virgin universe.
这些无限原石
These Infinity Stones
每一颗控制着一种本质的力量
each control an essential aspect of existence.
空间
Space.
现实
Reality.
力量
Power.
灵魂
Soul.
心灵
Mind.
还有时间
And Time.
再跟我说一遍他的名字
Tell me his name again.
灭霸
Thanos.
他就是灾难 托尼
He's a plague, Tony.
他侵略了无数星球 烧杀掠夺
He invades planets. He takes what he wants.
他灭掉了一半的人口
He wipes out half the population.
是他让洛基来的
He sent Loki.
纽约的那次袭击 他就是始作俑者
The attack on New York, that's him.
原来如此
This is it.
我们还有多少时间
What's our timeline?
不知道 他已经拥有了力量和空间原石
No telling. He has the Power and Space Stones.
这让他成了
That already makes him
全宇宙最为强大的人
the strongest creature in the whole universe.
如果他得到了六颗原石 托尼
If he gets his hands on all six stones, Tony...
他可以摧毁任何生命
He could destroy life
规模之大我们无法想象
on a scale hitherto undreamt of.
你竟然也会说"无法想象"
Did you seriously just say "Hitherto undreamt of"?
你竟然靠着宇宙大锅在拉筋
Are you seriously leaning on the Cauldron of the Cosmos?
你说这是什么
Is that what it is?
我宽宏大量不跟你计较
I'm going to allow that.
如果灭霸要集齐六颗原石 那我们为什么
If Thanos needs all six, why don't we just
不把你的这颗毁了呢
stick this one down a garbage disposal?
这绝不可行
No can do.
我们曾立誓用生命守护时间原石
We swore an oath to protect the Time Stone with our lives.
我还立誓要戒了冰激凌呢
And I swore off dairy...
谁知道后来班杰瑞用我的名字命名了一款口味
but then Ben & Jerry's named a flavor after me.
-史塔克狂热榛仁 -味道不错啊
- Stark Raving Hazelnuts. - Not bad.
有点腻了
A bit chalky.
大块浩克热巧克力是我们的最爱
A Hunk of Hulk of Burning Fudge is our favorite.
-真有这个东西 -随你便吧
- That's a thing? - Whatever.
重点是 事情已经变了
Point is, things change.
我们保护时间原石的誓言是不会变的
Our oath to protect the Time Stone cannot change.
而且这颗原石可能是我们对付灭霸的唯一有利机会
And this stone may be the best chance we have against Thanos.
是啊 但是反过来说
Yeah, so conversely,
如果我们不做好本职工作
it may also be his best chance against us.
这也可能是他对付我们的最好机会
Well, if we don't do our jobs.
话说你到底是做什么的
What is your job exactly?
除了捏个动物气球以外
Besides making balloon animals.
保护你们的现世 混球
Protecting your reality, douchebag.
好了 各位 我们能不能先不吵架
Okay, guys. Could we table this discussion right now?
好在我们有一颗原石
The fact is we have this stone.
我们知道它在哪儿
We know where it is.
幻视戴着心灵原石还不知道在哪儿呢
Vision is out there somewhere with the Mind Stone...
我们得尽快找到他
and we have to find him now.
我说的就是这件事
Yeah, that's the thing.
什么意思
What do you mean?
两周前 幻视关闭了他的通讯器
Two weeks ago, Vision turned off his transponder.
他失踪了
He's offline.
-什么 -你没听错
- What? - Yeah.
托尼 你又弄丢了一个超级机器人
Tony, you lost another super-bot?
我没有弄丢 他也不是机器人 他在进化
I didn't lose him. He's more than that. He's evolving.
那谁能找到幻视
Who could find Vision then?
该死
Shit.
或许史蒂夫·罗杰斯可以
Probably Steve Rogers.
噢 真好
Oh, great.
我是说可能
Maybe.
但是
But...
给他打电话啊
Call him.
没有你想得那么容易
It's not that easy.
天啊 我们是不是太久没见了
God, we haven't caught up in a spell, have we?
不是啊
No.
复仇者联盟解散了 我们玩完了
The Avengers broke up. We're toast.
解散
Broke up?
你是说像乐队一样 就像披头士
Like a band? Like... Like the Beatles?
队长和我吵得很凶
Cap and I fell out hard.
我们已经不说话了
We're not on speaking terms.
托尼 听我说
Tony, listen to me.
索尔已经死了
Thor's gone.
灭霸正在来的路上
Thanos is coming.
你跟谁说不说话已经不重要了
It doesn't matter who you're talking to or not.
破翻盖手机
Flip phone.
博士 不会是你自己
Say, Doc, you wouldn't happen to be
让头发动的吧
moving your hair, would ya?
这会儿不是
Not at the moment, no.
你没事吧
You okay?
-帮帮他 -班纳
- Help him! - Banner!
-王 快点 -快 快 这里交给我们
- Wong! Look alive! - Go, go! We got it!
星期五 这是什么情况
Friday, what am I looking at?
暂不确定 我正在查
Not sure. I'm working on it.
嘿 你最好把那个时间原石
Hey! You might wanna put that Time Stone
放进后面的口袋里 博士
in your back pocket, Doc!
我最好还是用上它
Might wanna use it.
内德 嘿 你转移一下大家的注意力
Ned, hey. I need you to cause a distraction.
我勒个去
Holy shit.
我们死定了
We're all gonna die!
天上有个宇宙飞船
There's a spaceship!
-怎么回事 -哦 天啊
- What's going on? - Oh, my God!
你们这帮孩子是咋回事
What's the matter with you kids?
没见过宇宙飞船是咋滴
You never seen a spaceship before?
星期五 疏散四十三大街南段的所有人
Friday, evac anyone south of 43rd Street.
通知应急救援
Notify first responders.
收到
Will do.
仔细听我说
Hear me and rejoice.
你们是即将
You are about to die
死于灭霸之子手下的人
at the hands of the Children of Thanos.
要心存感激
Be thankful...
你们这些渺小的生命是在做贡献
that your meaningless lives are now contributing...
不好意思 地球今天不营业
I'm sorry, Earth is closed today.
你赶紧打包滚吧
You better pack it up and get outta here.
原石守护者
Stonekeeper.
这个多嘴怪是在替你说话吗
Does this chattering animal speak for you?
当然不是了 我自己有嘴
Certainly not. I speak for myself.
你非法入侵了这个星球的这个城市
You're trespassing in this city and on this planet.
他的意思是让你赶紧滚 章鱼哥
He means get lost, Squidward.
他真让我心累
He exhausts me.
把原石给我拿过来
Bring me the stone.
班纳 你想变个身玩玩吗
Banner, you want a piece?
呃 不 不太想
Mmm, no, not really.
不过你们也没在乎过我的想法
But when do I ever get what I want?
这就对了
That's right.
好了 来吧
Okay. Push!
有一阵没见了
It's been a while.
你能回来帮忙真好 兄弟
It's gonna be good to have you, buddy.
好了 闭嘴
Okay. Shh.
让我 我需要集中精神
Let me just... I need to concentrate here for a second.
来吧 加把劲
Come on, come on, man.
天啊
God!
你的大伙伴呢
Where's your guy?
我不知道 我们之间好像有点小矛盾
I don't know. We've sorta been having a thing.
-可没时间闹小矛盾了 -我知道
- It's no time for a thing. - I know.
集中精力看着那边的那个东西
That's the thing right there. Let's go.
老哥 你让我在巫师面前丢脸了
Dude, you're embarrassing me in front of the wizards.
托尼 抱歉 不是我不行就是他不想
Tony, I'm sorry. Either I can't or he won't.
没事
It's okay.
你退后吧 麻烦你照顾一下他 谢谢
Hey, stand down. Keep an eye on him. Thank you.
-我罩他 -该死
- I have him. - Damn it.
这玩意从哪儿冒出来的
Where'd that come from?
这是纳米技术
It's nanotech.
你喜欢吗 是我最近在
You like it? A little something I...
班纳博士 如果你的小绿人朋友
Doctor Banner, if the rest of your green friend
不打算加入我们
won't be joining us...
得赶紧把原石送走
Gotta get that stone outta here, now.
石在我在
It stays with me.
正是如此 再见
Exactly. Bye.
托尼 你没事吧
Tony, you okay?
-怎么样了 赢面大不大 -挺好的
- How we doing? Good? Bad? - Really, really good.
赢面挺大 你打算出手相助吗
Really good. Do you plan on helping out?
我尽力了 他就是不出来
I'm trying. He won't come out.
小心铁锤
Hammer.
快出来 浩克 你这样算什么啊
Come on, Hulk! What are you doing to me?
快出来 快出来 快出来
Come out! Come out! Come out!
不
No!
"不"是什么意思
What do you mean, "No"?
嘿 史塔克先生 这是什么情况
Hey, man. What's up, Mr. Stark?
-小子 你从哪儿冒出来的 -我正在去现代美术馆参观的路上
- Kid, where'd you come from? - A field trip to MoMA.
这家伙是什么情况 史塔克先生
Uh, what is this guy's problem, Mr. Stark?
他是从宇宙来的
Uh, he's from space.
他是来偷走巫师的项链的
He came here to steal a necklace from a wizard.
你的把戏真有趣
Your powers are quaint.
你肯定很受小孩子欢迎
You must be popular with children.
这是个很简单的咒语 但很难解除
It's a simple spell but quite unbreakable.
那我就用你的死来破咒
Then I'll take it off your corpse.
要破解死人的咒语可不容易
You'll find removing a dead man's spell troublesome.
那就让你生不如死
You'll only wish you were dead.
不
No!
小家伙 那就是巫师 去救他
Kid, that's the wizard. Get on it.
这就去
On it!
你真阴
Not cool.
接到你了
Gotcha!
等一下
Wait!
史塔克先生 我要被吸上去了
Uh, Mr. Stark, I'm being beamed up.
坚持住 小子
Hang on, kid.
王 你一定要来参加我的婚礼
Wong, you're invited to my wedding.
给我加点料 星期五
Give me a little juice, Friday.
发射17A
Unlock 17A.
彼得 你快放手 我会接住你的
Pete, you gotta let go. I'm gonna catch you.
但你说要我救那个巫师
But you said save the wizard!
我不能呼吸了
I can't breathe.
我们飞得太高了 你会缺氧的
We're too high up. You're running out of air.
是哦 有道理
Yeah. That makes sense.
史塔克先生 这闻着像一辆新车
Mr. Stark, it smells like a new car in here!
旅途愉快 小子
Happy trails, kid.
-星期五 送他回家 -好的
- Friday, send him home. - Yep.
别啊
Oh, come on!
老板 波兹小姐来电
Boss, incoming call from Miss Potts.
托尼 我的天
Tony? Oh, my God.
你还好吗 出了什么事情
Are you all right? What's going on?
我没事 我只是在想
Yeah, I'm fine. I just think
我们八点半的约会可能要推迟了
we might have to push our 8:30 res.
为什么
Why?
我就是可能
Just 'cause I'll probably
短时间内赶不回去了
not make it back for a while.
告诉我你没在那艘船上
Tell me you're not on that ship.
我在
Yeah.
天呐 不 拜托你告诉我你没在那艘船上
God, no, please tell me you're not on the ship.
亲爱的 我很抱歉
Honey, I'm sorry.
对不起 我不知道该说什么
I'm sorry, I don't know what to say.
回来 托尼 我发誓
Come back here, Tony. I swear to God.
-佩珀 -你马上回来
- Pep. - Come back here right now.
回来
Come back.
老板 我们失去信号了
Boss, we're losing her.
我也快没信号了
I'm going too.
老天
Oh, my God!
我应该留在校车上的
I shoulda stayed on the bus.
你要去哪里
Where you going?
时间原石被夺走了
The Time Stone's been taken.
圣所现在无人看守
The Sanctum remains unguarded.
你接下来要怎么做
What will you do?
我要打个电话
I'm gonna make a call.
大声唱 德拉克斯
Sing it, Drax!
我们怎么又在干这事
Why are we doing this again?
那是个求救信号 火箭
It's a distress signal, Rocket.
有人可能要死了
Someone could be dying.
我知道 但我们为什么要去救人
I get that, but why are we doing it?
因为我们人美心善
'Cause we're nice.
而且不管那人是谁
And maybe whoever it is
有可能会给我们点小报酬
will give us a little cheddar cheese for our effort.
-那不是重点 -那不是重点
- Which isn't the point. - Which isn't the point.
我是说 如果他没钱
I mean, if he doesn't pony up...
我们就占了他的船
We take his ship.
-没错 -正确
- Exactly! - Bingo!
就这么决定了
All right!
我们要到了
We are arriving.
好了 守护者们
All right, Guardians,
不要忘记前方或许有危险
don't forget this might be dangerous...
所以我们要先摆出一副恶人脸
so let's put on our mean faces.
格鲁特 马上把那玩意儿放下
Groot, put that thing away, now.
我不想再说第二遍
I don't wanna tell you again.
格鲁特
Groot.
我是格鲁特
I am Groot!
-哇哦 -注意用词
- Whoa! - Language!
-嘿 -哇
- Hey! - Wow.
你翅膀硬了啊 小子
You got some acorns on you, kid.
自从你长大了一点
Ever since you got a little sap,
就是个十足的小混蛋
you're a total d-hole.
你要是继续玩 我就把那玩意砸个粉碎
Now, keep it up, and I'm gonna smash that thing to pieces.
出了什么事情
What happened?
天呐
Oh, my God.
看来我们是得不到报酬了
Looks like we're not getting paid.
开雨刷 开雨刷
Wipers! Wipers!
把那东西刷下去
Get it off.
这小子究竟是怎么活下来的
How the hell is this dude still alive?
他不是个小子
He is not a dude.
你才是小子
You're a dude.
他 他是个男人
This... This is a man.
一个英俊潇洒 肌肉发达的男人
A handsome, muscular man.
我肌肉发达啊
I'm muscular.
得了吧 奎尔
But who are you kidding, Quill?
你就是块五花肉
You're one sandwich away from fat.
呵呵
Yeah, right.
是真的 奎尔 你最近胖了
It's true, Quill. You have put on weight.
什么
What?
卡魔拉 你也觉得我
Gamora, do you think I'm...
他很焦虑 愤怒
He is anxious, angry.
他痛失了很多 心怀愧疚
He feels tremendous loss and guilt.
他就像是海盗和天使生的孩子
It's like a pirate had a baby with an angel.
哇哦
Wow.
这一句还真是敲醒了我 好吧
This is a real wake-up call for me. Okay.
我要买台跑步机 说到做到
I'm gonna get a Bowflex. I'm gonna commit.
我还要买哑铃
I'm gonna get some dumbbells.
哑铃是不能吃的 好吗
You know you can't eat dumbbells, right?
他的肌肉就像是
It's like his muscles
用科塔蒂金属纤维造成的
are made of Cotati metal fibers.
别再摸他的肌肉了
Stop massaging his muscles.
叫醒他
Wake him up.
醒醒
Wake.
你们是谁
Who the hell are you guys?
我认识灭霸这么久 他一直就只有一个目标
The entire time I knew Thanos, he only ever had one goal.
通过消除宇宙一半的生命
To bring balance to the universe
来维持宇宙的平衡
by wiping out half of all life.
他曾经一个星球接一个星球地杀人
He used to kill people planet by planet,
一次又一次的大屠杀
massacre by massacre.
包括我的星球
Including my own.
他要是得到了六颗原石
If he gets all six Infinity Stones...
他打个响指就能除掉一半的人
he can do it with the snap of his fingers like this.
你似乎很了解灭霸
You seem to know a great deal about Thanos.
卡魔拉是灭霸的女儿
Gamora is the daughter of Thanos.
你父亲杀死了我弟弟
Your father killed my brother.
真狗血啊
Oh, boy.
严格来讲 是养女
Stepfather, technically.
她跟你一样恨灭霸
And she hates him as much as you do.
家家有本难念的经
Families can be tough.
我父亲死之前
Before my father died,
他告诉我 我有个同父异母的姐姐
he told me that I had a half-sister...
他把她关在地狱
that he imprisoned in Hel.
然后她回家了 戳瞎了我的眼睛
And then she returned home and stabbed me in the eye.
所以我不得不杀了她
So I had to kill her.
我想生活就是这样 不是吗
That's life though, isn't it, I guess.
冤冤相报何时了
Goes round and round and...
我懂你的难处
I feel your pain.
我也懂你的难处 因为
I feel your pain as well, because...
我是说 虽然我不想跟你们比较
I mean, it's not a competition,
但我也过得很惨
but I've been through a lot.
我爸爸杀了我妈妈
My father killed my mother.
然后我又杀了我爸爸
And then I had to kill my father.
真的很难
That was hard.
可能比杀死姐姐要难一点
Probably even harder than having to kill a sister.
至少我的眼睛都还在 所以
Plus, I came out with both my eyes, which was...
我要的是锤子 不是汤勺
I need a hammer, not a spoon.
我要怎么启动这东西 有没有密码之类的 呃
How do I open this thing? Is there some sort of, uh...
四位数的密码 有可能是生日
A four-digit code, maybe? Maybe a birthdate.
-你在做什么 -开走你们的分离舱
- Uh, what are you doing? - Taking your pod.
不 不可以
No, you're not.
我不允许你驾驶我们的分离舱 先生
You will not be taking our pod today, sir.
额 奎尔 你是故意把你的声音压低吗
Uh... Quill, are you making your voice deeper?
-没有 -你有
- No. - You are.
你在模仿那位男神 很怪
You're imitating the god-man. It's weird.
没有 我没有
No, I'm not.
-他又模仿了一次 -我的声音本来就这样
- He just did it again! - This is my voice.
你是在嘲笑我吗
Are you mocking me?
-你是在嘲笑我吗 -够了 你又在学我
- Are you mocking me? - Stop it. You did it again.
他在模仿我
He's trying to copy me.
你最好别再学我说话
I need you to stop doing that.
-够了 -是他先开始的
- Enough! - He's doing it first.
我们要阻止灭霸
We need to stop Thanos.
也就是说 我们需要搞清楚
Which means we need to find out
他下一步是去哪里
where he's going next.
虚无知地[哪儿也不去]
Knowhere.
他肯定是要去什么地方的
He must be going somewhere.
不是吧 虚无知地
No, no. Knowhere?
那是个地名 我们去过 那地方太烂了
It's a place. We've been there. It sucks.
-不好意思 那是我们的食物 -现在是我的了
- Excuse me, that's our food. - Not anymore.
索尔 他为什么要去虚无知地
Thor, why would he go to Knowhere?
因为现实原石
Because for years...
安全无恙地被寄放在那里好几年了
the Reality Stone's been safely stored there
在一个叫收藏者的人手里
with a man called the Collector.
如果是在收藏者手里 那就不安全了
If it's with the Collector, then it's not safe.
蠢货才会把原石交给他呢
Only an idiot would give that man a stone.
-天才也会 -你怎么知道
- Or a genius. - How do you know...
他不会去找其他原石
he's not going for one of the other stones?
无限原石一共有六颗
There are six stones out there.
灭霸上星期毁灭山达尔星时
Thanos already has the Power Stone...
从那里得到了力量原石
because he stole it last week when he decimated Xandar.
他毁了我的船
He stole the Space Stone from me...
屠杀了我一半的子民 又从我手上夺走了空间原石
when he destroyed my ship and slaughtered half my people.
时间原石和心灵原石在地球上很安全
The Time and Mind Stones are safe on Earth.
由复仇者联盟守护着
They're with the Avengers.
-复仇者联盟 -地球上最强大的英雄们
- The Avengers? - Earth's mightiest heroes.
像凯文·贝肯那样的吗
Like Kevin Bacon?
他可能也是队里一员吧 我不知道
He may be on the team. I don't know.
我很久没去地球了
I haven't been there in a while.
至于灵魂原石 没人见过这颗原石
As for the Soul Stone, well, no one's ever seen that.
也没人知道它在哪里
No one even knows where it is.
因此灭霸得不到这颗原石
Therefore Thanos can't get it.
所以他会先去虚无知地
Therefore he's going to Knowhere.
因为他要去找现实原石
Hence he'll be getting the Reality Stone.
不用谢
You're welcome.
那我们现在就得去虚无知地
Then we have to go to Knowhere now.
不对 我们要去的地方是尼德威阿尔
Wrong. Where we have to go is Nidavellir.
-这词是你编的吧 -所有词都是编的
- That's a made-up word. - All words are made up.
真有尼德威阿尔这个地方 没开玩笑吧
Nidavellir is real? Seriously?
那地方是一个传奇
That place is a legend.
他们制造出最强大 最可怕的
They make the most powerful, horrific weapons
让整个宇宙都饱受折磨的武器
to ever torment the universe.
我倒是很想去一下这地方
I would very much like to go there, please.
这只兔子说得对
The rabbit is correct
很明显他是你们之中最聪明的了
and clearly the smartest among you.
兔子
Rabbit?
只有矮人伊特里能打造出我需要的武器
Only Eitri the Dwarf can make me the weapon I need.
我想你就是队长吧 先生
I assume you're the captain, sir.
好眼力
You're very perceptive.
你看着像是个道德高尚的好队长
You seem like a noble leader.
你愿意和我一起去探访尼德威阿尔吗
Will you join me on my quest to Nidavellir?
请让我请示一下我们的队长 等等 我就是队长
Let me just ask the captain. Oh, wait a second, it's me!
-没问题 我去 -很好
- Yeah. I'll go. - Wonderful!
呃 我才是队长
Uh, except for that I'm the captain.
奎尔
Quiet.
-那是我的背包 -去坐好
- That's my backpack. - Go sit down.
听着 这是我的飞船
Look, this is my ship.
我不会去
And I'm not goin' to...
等等 我们在说什么武器来着
Wait, what kinda weapon are we talkin' about here?
能杀死灭霸的那种
The Thanos-killing kind.
你不觉得那样的武器我们应该人手一把吗
Don't you think that we should all have a weapon like that?
不觉得 你力气不够 驾驭不了那样的武器
No. You simply lack the strength to wield them.
当你的精神不稳定时
Your bodies would crumble
你的身体会不堪一击
as your minds collapsed into madness.
你这么一说我更想试试了 是不是很奇怪
Is it weird that I wanna do it even more now?
是有点奇怪
Mmm, a little bit, yeah.
如果我们不去虚无知地
If we don't go to Knowhere
让灭霸再得到一颗原石的话
and Thanos retrieves another stone...
那他会强大得无法阻止
he'll be too powerful to stop.
-他已经是了 -我想到办法了
- He already is. - I got it figured out.
我们有两艘船
We got two ships
和一大群蠢货
and a large assortment of morons.
那么 我和格鲁特跟着海盗天使走
So me and Groot will go with the pirate angel here.
剩下的蠢货去虚无知地
And the morons will go to Knowhere
试着阻止灭霸
to try to stop Thanos.
-同意吗 同意 -非常同意
- Cool? Cool. - So cool.
郑重声明
For the record...
我知道你之所以跟他走
I know that you're going with him
是因为那里没有灭霸
because it's where Thanos isn't.
你知道的 你真的不该
You know, you really shouldn't
这样跟你的队长说话 奎尔
talk that way to your captain, Quill.
走吧 格鲁特
Come on, Groot.
别玩游戏了 脑子都玩坏了
Put that game down. You'll rot your brain.
就此告别 祝你们好运 蠢货们
I bid you farewell and good luck, morons.
拜
Bye.
幻视
Vis?
原石又有反映了吗
Is it the stone again?
它好像在跟我说些什么
It's as if it's speaking to me.
它说了什么
What does it say?
我不 我不知道 但确实想要告诉我什么
I don't... I don't know, but something.
嘿
Hey.
告诉我 你感受到了什么
Tell me what you feel.
我只感受到了你
I just feel you.
十点钟有班车去格拉斯哥
So there's a 10:00 a.M. To Glasgow...
这样在你回去之前 我们能多待一会儿
which would give us more time together before you went back.
万一我错过那班车怎么办
What if I miss that train?
十一点还有一班
There's an 11:00.
如果我错过了所有的班车呢
What if I missed all the trains?
如果我这次去了就回不来呢
What if this time I didn't go back?
但你已经答应史塔克了
But you gave Stark your word.
我宁愿承诺于你
I'd rather give it to you.
你知道的 也有人在等着我回去的
Well, there are people who are expecting me too, you know.
我们都做出了承诺
We both made promises.
但不是对彼此
Not to each other.
旺达
Wanda.
两年了 我们偷得这些许时光
For two years, we've stolen these moments...
试着证明我们俩之间有可能
trying to see if this could work and...
我不知道
I don't know.
你知道的 我只是想为我自己说几句
You know what, I'm just gonna speak for myself.
我想
I think...
-有可能的 -有可能的
- It works. - It works.
有可能的
It works.
留下吧
Stay.
别离开我
Stay with me.
或者不留也行 可能是我太心急了
Or not. If I'm overstepping...
他们是什么
What are they?
是原石要传达给我的警告
What the stone was warning me about.
我得走了
I have to go.
不 幻视
No, Vision.
幻视 如果是真的
Vision, if that's true,
那么离开或许不是好主意
then maybe going isn't the best idea.
旺达 我
Wanda, I...
幻视
Vision!
那刀 封住了我的力量
The blade, it stopped me from phasing.
-这有可能吗 -本来是不可能的
- Is that even possible? - It isn't supposed to be.
我的系统开始失灵了
My systems are failing.
我觉得我们当初真应该待在床上的
I'm beginning to think we should have stayed in bed.
幻视
Vis!
交出原石 我就饶她一命
Give up the stone, and she lives.
放开他
Hands off.
来 快点
Come on. Come on.
加油 你得站起来
Come on, you gotta get up.
你得站起来 快
You gotta get up. Come on. Hey.
我们得赶紧走
Hey. We have to go.
求你了 求你快走吧
Please. Please leave.
是你让我留下来的
You asked me to stay.
-我哪也不去 -求你了
- I'm staying. - Please.
-起来 -我做不到
- Get up. - I can't.
我们不想赶尽杀绝 但不代表我们不会
We don't wanna kill you, but we will.
你们绝不会再有可乘之机了
You'll never get the chance again.
你能站起来吗
Can you stand?
谢了 队长
Thank you, Captain.
到飞机上再说
Let's get you on the jet.
我以为我们说好了的
Now, I thought we had a deal.
不单独行动 及时汇报 不冒险
Stay close, check in, don't take any chances.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们只想单独在一起
We just wanted time.
去哪 队长
Where to, Cap?
回家
Home.
我们会没事的 会没事的
We'll be safe. We'll be safe.
泽侯贝里族民们
Zehobereians.
妈妈 我的妈妈在哪
Mother! Where's my mother?
顺我者昌 逆我者亡
Choose a side or die.
妈妈
Mother!
一边 是审判日般的灭亡
One side is a revelation...
而另一边则是鲜为人知的无尚荣耀
the other an honor known only to a few.
怎么了 小家伙
What's wrong, little one?
我妈妈不见了 她在哪里
My mother. Where is my mother?
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
卡魔拉
Gamora.
你可真是个小战士 卡魔拉
You're quite the fighter, Gamora.
来吧
Come.
让我来帮你
Let me help you.
看
Look.
很漂亮 对吧
Pretty, isn't it?
完美的平衡 正是世间万物应有的样子
Perfectly balanced, as all things should be.
如果其中一方过重
Too much to one side or the other...
给你 你来试试
Here. You try.
你们就安心前往天国 去见造物主吧
Now, go in peace to meet your maker.
别看
Uh-uh.
专心一点
Concentrate.
看 你已经学会了
There. You've got it.
卡魔拉
Gamora.
你说这些手榴弹是那种炸烂小丁丁型的
Do you know if these grenades
还是瓦斯型的
are the blow-off-your-junk kind or the gas kind?
因为我在考虑
Because I was thinking about
挂几个在我的腰带上
hanging a couple on my belt right here.
但如果这是那种类型就不好了
But I don't want to if they're the...
我想求你帮个忙
I need to ask a favor.
当然 说吧
Yeah, sure.
不管发生什么
One way or another,
我们最终肯定会跟灭霸交手
the path that we're on leads to Thanos.
是啊 所以我才准备这些手榴弹
Which is what the grenades are for.
抱歉跑题了 你要我帮什么忙
Uh, I'm sorry. What's the favor?
如果进展不顺
If things go wrong...
如果灭霸抓到了我
If Thanos gets me...
我要你对我保证
I want you to promise me...
你会杀了我
you'll kill me.
什么
What?
我知道一些他不知道的秘密
I know something he doesn't.
如果被他发现
And if he finds it out,
整个宇宙都会处于危险之中
the entire universe could be at risk.
什么秘密
What do you know?
如果我告诉你 你也会知道的
If I tell you, you'd know too.
但如果这件事这么重要
If it's so important...
我不应该知道吗
shouldn't I?
除非你想自寻死路
Only if you wanna die.
为什么非得假设有个人会牺牲呢
Why does somebody always have to die in this scenario?
你只要
Just...
相信我 很有可能需要杀了我
Trust me. And possibly kill me.
呃 我很乐意
I mean, I'd like to.
我真的愿意 但你
I really would. But you...
向我发誓
Swear to me.
以你母亲的名义发誓
Swear to me on your mother.
好吧
Okay.
我发誓
-噢 -大哥
- Oh. - Dude.
你站在那儿多久了
How long have you been standing there?
一个小时
An hour.
An hour?
你是在开玩笑吗
Are you serious?
我最近掌握了一个技能
I've mastered the ability
我只要站在这里一动不动
of standing so incredibly still...
肉眼就看不到我
that I become invisible to the eye.
看吧
Watch.
你不是在吃坚果吗
You're eating a zarg-nut.
但我的动作
But my movement...
非常之慢
was so slow...
你们根本感觉不到
that it's imperceptible.
呃 并没有
Mmm, no.
我很确定我隐形了
I'm sure I'm invisible.
嗨 德拉克斯
Hi, Drax.
该死
Damn it.
这个地方看起来好荒凉
This place looks deserted.
我正在获取第三象限的动态
I'm reading movement in the third quadrant.
我也收到了
Yep, I'm picking that up too.
我们就在这降落吧
Let's put down right here.
原石不在我这儿
I don't have it.
银河系的所有人都知道
Everyone in the galaxy knows
你为了自己
you'd sell your own brother...
哪怕是那一点点的蝇头小利
if you thought it would add even the slightest trinket...
都不惜出卖自己的亲兄弟
to your pathetic collection.
我知道你有现实原石 蒂万
I know you have the Reality Stone, Tivan.
交给我你就不用受折磨
Giving it to me will spare you a great deal of suffering.
我跟你说过
I told you.
我已经卖掉了
I sold it.
我有什么理由对你说谎呢
Why would I lie?
我认为说谎对你来说像呼吸一样稀松平常
I imagine it's like breathing for you.
说谎就是找死
Like suicide.
看来你明白我的意思
You do understand.
就算是你 也不愿意白白交出如此珍贵的东西
Not even you would surrender something so precious.
我不知道它的来历
I didn't know what it was.
那你比我想象中的还要愚蠢
Then you're more of a fool than I took you for.
就是他
It's him.
我再给你最后一次机会 谎话精
Last chance, charlatan.
原石在哪里
Where's the stone?
今天
Today...
德拉克斯 德拉克斯
Drax. Drax.
就是你为我的妻女血债血偿的日子
...he pays for the deaths of my wife and daughter.
德拉克斯 等等
Drax, wait.
还不行 还不是时候
Not yet, not yet, not yet.
德拉克斯
Drax.
德拉克斯 德拉克斯 听我说
Drax, Drax, Drax. Listen to me.
他还没有拿到原石
He doesn't have the stone yet.
如果我们能拿到 我们就可以阻止他
If we get it, then we can stop him.
首要任务是拿到原石
We have to get the stone first. Yeah.
不
No.
不 为了奥维特 为了卡马利亚
No. For Ovette, for Camaria.
沉睡吧
Sleep.
好了
Okay.
卡魔拉 曼蒂斯 你们走右边
Gamora, Mantis, you go right.
是你们的右边
The other right.
为什么
Why?
为什么是你 女儿
Why you, daughter?
真够快的
That was quick.
妙极了 真是妙极了 妙极了
Magnificent! Magnificent! Magnificent!
你是在为我难过吗 女儿
Is that sadness I sense in you, daughter?
我知道 你还是在乎我的
In my heart, I knew you still cared.
果然还是眼见为实啊
But one never knows for sure.
现实总是令人失望
Reality is often disappointing.
它曾是如此
That is, it was.
但如今
Now...
现实由我掌控了
reality can be whatever I want.
你知道我会来
You knew I'd come.
我等着你来呢
I counted on it.
我们还有些事情要谈 小家伙
There's something we need to discuss, little one.
灭霸
Thanos!
不
No!
放了她 奶昔大哥
Let her go, Grimace.
彼特
Peter.
我让你走右边的
I told you to go right.
现在还要跟我争这个
Now? Really?
放了她
You let her go!
原来是小男朋友啊
Ah, the boyfriend.
不
No.
我更像是一个
Like to think of myself
随叫随到 专杀泰坦星人的职业杀手
more as a Titan-killing, long-term booty call.
-放了她 -彼特
- Let her go. - Peter.
不然我就打爆你那螺丝帽一样的下巴
I'm gonna blow that nutsack of a chin right off your face.
你要杀的不是他
Not him.
你答应过我的 你答应过的
You promised. You promised.
噢 女儿
Oh, daughter.
你对他的期望太高了
You expect too much from him.
是她要求你这样做的 是吗
She's asked, hasn't she?
开枪吧
Do it.
哼
Mmm.
开枪
Do it!
我让你走右边的
I told you to go right.
我爱你胜过一切
I love you more than anything.
我也爱你
I love you too.
我喜欢这小子
I like him.
还没有幻视的消息吗
Still no word from Vision?
卫星在爱丁堡的某个地方失去了他的信号
Satellites lost him somewhere over Edinburgh.
他在一辆被盗的昆式战斗机上
On a stolen Quinjet
和四个世界上最高通缉的罪犯一起
with four of the world's most wanted criminals.
他们之所以是罪犯
You know they're only criminals because
都是因为你们 不是吗 长官
you've chosen to call them that, right, sir?
我的天 罗德斯
My God, Rhodes.
你比我还能说谎
Your talent for horseshit rivals my own.
如果不是因为那些协定
If it weren't for those Accords,
幻视现在就在这里
Vision would've been right here.
我可记得那协定上有你的亲笔签名呢 上校
I remember your signature on those papers, Colonel.
这倒没错
That's right.
我也很肯定我为此付出了代价
And I'm pretty sure I paid for that.
你犹豫了吗
You have second thoughts?
不再犹豫了
Not anymore.
国务卿先生
Mr. Secretary.
你们胆子可真大
You got some nerve.
这是我对你们的评价
I'll give you that.
现在需要胆量的是你
You could use some of that right now.
世界现在水深火热
The world's on fire.
你们以为之前的账就此一笔勾销了吗
And you think all is forgiven?
我不是来寻求原谅的
I'm not looking for forgiveness.
我也早就不再征求允许了
And I'm way past asking permission.
地球刚刚失去了她最好的守护者
Earth just lost her best defender.
所以我们是来战斗的
So we're here to fight.
如果你想挡我们的道
And if you wanna stand in our way...
我们会把你也拿下
we'll fight you too.
逮捕他们
Arrest them.
没问题
All over it.
估计我得上军事法庭了
That's a court-martial.
很高兴见到你 队长
It's great to see you, Cap.
我也是 罗迪
You too, Rhodey.
嘿
Hey.
哇 你们
Wow. You guys...
看上去真是一团糟
really look like crap.
这几年过得不怎么样吧
Must've been a rough couple years.
是啊 又不是天天住五星级酒店
Yeah, well, the hotels weren't exactly five star.
我觉得你们看上去棒极了
Uh, I think you look great.
呃
Uh...
没错 我回来了
Yeah, I'm back.
嗨 布鲁斯
Hi, Bruce.
小娜
Nat.
尴尬了
This is awkward.
他们一定会回来的是吧
So we gotta assume they're coming back, right?
而且他们肯定能找到我们
And they can clearly find us.
我们得全员待命 克林特去哪了
We need all hands on deck. Where's Clint?
签署协议的那件事以后
After the whole Accords situation,
他和斯科特都达成了协议 他们要为家庭考虑
he and Scott took a deal. It was too tough
现在都被软禁在家里
on their families. They're on house arrest.
-斯科特是谁 -蚁人
- Who's Scott? - Ant-Man.
我们有了蜘蛛侠又来个蚁人吗
There's an Ant-Man and a Spider-Man?
好了 听着
Okay, look.
灭霸拥有宇宙中最强大的军队
Thanos has the biggest army in the universe...
他不拿到幻视的原石
and he is not gonna stop until he gets...
绝不会罢休
Vision's stone.
那我们必须保护好它
Then we have to protect it.
不 我们必须毁了它
No, we have to destroy it.
我头顶的这颗原石
I've been giving a good deal of thought
我想了很久
to this entity in my head.
关于它的性质
About its nature.
还有它的组成
But also its composition.
我觉得如果它被暴露在
I think if it were exposed
一个和它性质相同的
to a sufficiently powerful energy source...
无比巨大的能量源之下 也许
something very similar to its own signature, perhaps...
它的分子完整性将会被破坏
its molecular integrity could fail.
是啊 你也一样
Yeah, and you with it.
我是不会同意的
We're not having this conversation.
毁掉这颗原石 是唯一能确保
Eliminating the stone is the only way
灭霸得不到它的方式
to be certain that Thanos can't get it.
这代价太高了
That's too high a price.
只有你有能力付出这个代价
Only you have the power to pay it.
灭霸正威胁着半个宇宙
Thanos threatens half the universe.
不能让一条生命阻碍我们的行动
One life cannot stand in the way of defeating him.
但确实会
But it should.
我们不拿性命做交换 幻视
We don't trade lives, Vision.
队长 七十年前 你放弃自己的生命
Captain, 70 years ago, you laid down your life...
救了数百万人
to save how many millions of people?
告诉我 这两者有什么区别
Tell me, why is this any different?
因为你可能还有选择
Because you might have a choice.
你的大脑
Your mind is made up
是由一些复杂的覆盖网络构成的
of a complex construct of overlays.
贾维斯 奥创 托尼 我 还有原石
Jarvis, Ultron, Tony, me, the stone.
所有这些结合在一起
All of them mixed together,
在你体内取长补短
all of them learning from one another.
你是说幻视并不只是原石而已吗
You're saying Vision isn't just the stone?
我是说如果我们取出原石
I'm saying that if we take out the stone...
还会有很大一部分的幻视存在
there's still a whole lot of Vision left.
或许还是最精华的部分
Perhaps the best parts.
我们可以做到吗
Can we do that?
我不行 这儿也没有条件
Not me, not here.
那你最好快点找到
Well, you better find someone
能做这件事的人和地点
and somewhere fast.
罗斯不可能这么轻易地
Ross isn't just gonna let you guys
放过你们
have your old rooms back.
我知道一个地方
I know somewhere.
国王护卫队
The Kingsguard
和女子皇家亲卫队都在待命中
and the Dora Milaje have been alerted.
边境部落呢
And the Border Tribe?
他们留守边境
Those that are left.
也给贾巴里部落传个话
Send word to the Jabari as well.
姆巴库喜欢打仗
M'Baku likes a good fight.
那他呢
And what of this one?
这个人可能已经厌倦了战争
This one may be tired of war.
但是白狼已经休整够了
But the White Wolf has rested long enough.
什么时候开战
Where's the fight?
马上
On its way.
我为灭霸做事这么久
In all the time I've served Thanos...
从没让他失望过
I have never failed him.
如果原石还镶在
If I were to reach our rendezvous on Titan...
你这个讨厌的人身上
with the Time Stone still attached
而我却两手空空地回到泰坦星见他
to your vaguely irritating person...
那可就说不过去了
there would be judgment.
把原石
Give me...
给我
the stone.
哇 你还真是
Wow, you're a seriously
一件忠心耿耿的披风啊
loyal piece of outerwear, aren't you?
呃 说到忠心耿耿
Yeah, uh, speaking of loyalty...
你怎么
What the...
-我知道您要说什么 -你不该来这里
- I know what you're gonna say. - You should not be here.
-我本来要回家的 -我不想听
- I was gonna go home. - I don't wanna hear it.
但我家那么远 我在半路上
But it was such a long way down and I just thought
-想到了您 -现在也不得不听着了
- about you on the way... - And now I gotta hear it.
而且我还被卡在了飞船的一边
...and kinda stuck to the side of the ship.
顺便一说 这套战衣好像也感觉到了危险
And this suit is ridiculously intuitive, by the way.
该死
God damn it.
所以 如果非要说的话 其实我在这里也怪你
So, if anything, it's kinda your fault that I'm here.
-你说什么 -我收回
- What did you just say? - I take that back.
现在我已经在太空里了
And now, I'm here in space.
是啊 就在我最不想让你来的地方
Yeah, right where I didn't want you to be.
这不是康尼岛 不是出外勤
This isn't Coney Island. This isn't a field trip.
这儿可是有去无回
This is a one-way ticket.
你明白了吗 别假装你已经想清楚了
You hear me? Don't pretend you thought this through.
我确实想清楚了
No, I did think this through.
你怎么可能想清楚
You could not have possibly thought this through.
如果整个社区都没了
You can't be a friendly neighborhood Spider-Man...
我如何当个友好的社区蜘蛛侠
if there's no neighborhood.
好吧 好像这么说也不对
Okay, that didn't really make sense,
但你知道我想表达什么
but you know what I'm trying to say.
好吧 我们现在有个状况
Come on. We got a situation.
看见下面那个人了吗 他有麻烦了
See him down there? He's in trouble.
你有什么计划吗
What's your plan?
-说 -呃
- Go. - Um...
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay... Uh...
你看过一部非常老的电影吗 叫《异形》
Okay. Did you ever see this really old movie, Aliens?
很痛苦吧 是不是
Painful, aren't they?
这些针最初是在显微外科手术中使用的
They were originally designed for microsurgery.
而其中的任意一根
And any one of them...
都能瞬间结束你朋友的生命
could end your friend's life in an instant.
实话实说 他其实不是我的朋友
I gotta tell you, he's not really my friend.
救他的命其实只是出于职业素养而已
Saving his life is more of a professional courtesy.
你还没救成呢
You've saved nothing.
你的力量和我相比
Your powers are inconsequential
根本不值一提
compared to mine.
是啊 但那孩子看的电影更多
Yeah, but the kid's seen more movies.
太棒了 等等 那些是什么
Yes! Wait. What are those?
嗨 咱们还没有正式见过面呢
Hey, we haven't officially met.
好吧
Cool.
我们要调转航向
We gotta turn this ship around.
是啊 现在你倒是想逃了 真是一个好计划
Yeah, now he wants to run. Great plan.
不 我想保护原石
No, I want to protect the stone.
我还想听你感谢我呢
And I want you to thank me.
现在说吧 我听着呢
Now, go ahead. I'm listening.
谢你什么 差点把我炸进太空吗
For what? Nearly blasting me into space?
是谁刚刚救了你这个大魔术师啊 是我
Who just saved your magical ass? Me.
我真的不知道
I seriously don't know
你是怎么把你的大脑袋塞进那个头盔里的
how you fit your head into that helmet.
承认吧 我叫你闪开的时候你就应该照做
Admit it, you should've ducked out when I told you to.
我想要你老实待着 而你拒绝了
I tried to bench you. You refused.
我不像你生命中的其他人 我不听命于你
Unlike everyone else in your life, I don't work for you.
正因为你不听话
And due to that fact,
我们现在在一个会飞的甜甜圈里
we're now in a flying doughnut...
离地球几百万里远 还没有后援
billions of miles from Earth with no backup.
-我是后援 -不 你是偷跑上来的
- I'm backup. - No, you're a stowaway.
大人说话 小孩别插嘴
The adults are talking.
对不起 我搞不清楚你们的关系了
I'm sorry, I'm confused as to the relationship here.
他是谁 你的保镖吗
What is he, your ward?
不
No.
-我是彼得 -斯特兰奇博士
- I'm Peter, by the way. - Doctor Strange.
要用艺名啊
Oh, you're using our made-up names. Um...
那我是蜘蛛侠
I'm Spider-Man, then.
这架飞船正在自动矫正航线
This ship is self-correcting its course.
现在是自动驾驶模式
Thing's on autopilot.
我们能控制它吗
Can we control it?
载我们回家
Fly us home?
-史塔克 -怎么了
- Stark? - Yeah.
你能带我们回去吗
Can you get us home?
我听到你的话了
Yeah, I heard you.
我只是在想 我不太确定我们应该回去
I'm thinking I'm not so sure we should.
无论如何
Under no circumstances
我们都不能把时间原石送到灭霸的手中
can we bring the Time Stone to Thanos.
我觉得你还没有
I don't think you quite understand
搞清楚现在的局势
what's at stake here.
什么 不 是你不懂
What? No. It's you who doesn't understand...
自从他派军到纽约时起
that Thanos has been inside my head for six years.
灭霸已经在我的脑海中盘踞六年了
Since he sent an army to New York
而现在他回来了
and now he's back.
而我不知道应该做什么
And I don't know what to do.
所以我不确定
So I'm not so sure
这场战役是在我们还是他的地盘上打更好
if it's a better plan to fight him on our turf or his...
但他们的所作所为 他们的能力 你都看见了
but you saw what they did, what they can do.
至少在他的地盘上 可以打他个措手不及
At least on his turf, he's not expecting it.
所以我说 我们将战火引到他那儿
So I say we take the fight to him.
博士
Doctor.
你同意吗
Do you concur?
好吧 史塔克 我们去找他
All right, Stark. We go to him.
但你必须要明白
But you have to understand...
如果我需要在救你 还有那个孩子
if it comes to saving you
和时间原石中做选择的话
or the kid or the Time Stone...
我会毫不犹豫地放弃你们俩的生命
I will not hesitate to let either of you die.
我不能失去原石 整个宇宙的希望都在它身上
I can't, because the universe depends on it.
很好 提前说清楚道德标准
Nice. Good, moral compass.
那就这样说定了
We're straight.
好了 孩子
All right, kid.
你正式是复仇者的一员了
You're an Avenger now.
我觉得你可能饿了
I thought you might be hungry.
我一直恨那把椅子
I always hated that chair.
我听说了
So I've been told.
即便这样 我也希望你有一天能坐上它
Even so, I'd hoped you'd sit in it one day.
我恨这个房间
I hated this room.
这架飞船
This ship.
我恨我的人生
I hated my life.
你也跟我说过了
You told me that too.
每一天
Every day.
我听了近二十年
For almost 20 years.
你带走我时 我还只是个孩子
I was a child when you took me.
我救了你
I saved you.
不
No.
不是 我们曾经快乐地生活在我的母星上
No. We were happy on my home planet.
每天在饥饿中入睡
Going to bed hungry...
以拾荒为生
scrounging for scraps.
你的星球已经在崩溃的边缘了
Your planet was on the brink of collapse.
是我拯救了那一切
I'm the one who stopped that.
你知道后来发生了什么吗
Do you know what's happened since then?
新生儿们
The children born...
在蓝天下过着富足的生活
have known nothing but full bellies and clear skies.
那里成了天堂
It's a paradise.
因为你杀掉了星球上一半的人
Because you murdered half the planet.
那只是为了救赎而付出的小小代价而已
A small price to pay for salvation.
你疯了
You're insane.
小家伙 这是一道简单的算术题
Little one, it's a simple calculus.
宇宙是有限的 它的资源也是有限的
This universe is finite, its resources finite.
如果对生命不加以约束 它最终将走向消亡
If life is left unchecked, life will cease to exist.
它需要矫正
It needs correction.
你不能妄下定论
You don't know that!
我是唯一一个看清的人
I'm the only one who knows that.
至少我是唯一愿意付出行动的
At least, I'm the only one with the will to act on it.
曾经
For a time...
与我并肩战斗的你
you had that same will...
也有着共同的信仰
as you fought by my side.
女儿
Daughter.
我不是你的女儿
I'm not your daughter.
我痛恨你教给我的一切东西
Everything I hate about myself you taught me.
正是这些
And, in doing so,
让你成为银河中最勇敢无畏的女人
made you the fiercest woman in the galaxy.
所以我当时才派你去寻找灵魂原石
That's why I trusted you to find the Soul Stone.
抱歉我让你失望了
I'm sorry I disappointed you.
我的确很失望
I am disappointed.
但不是因为你没有找到
But not because you didn't find it.
而是因为你找到了
But because you did.
却对我说谎了
And you lied.
星云
Nebula.
不要这样
Don't do this.
不久以前
Some time ago,
你妹妹潜入这架飞船来刺杀我
your sister snuck aboard this ship to kill me.
求求你 别这样
Please don't do this.
她差点就成功了
And very nearly succeeded.
所以我把她带到这里
So I brought her here.
来谈一谈
To talk.
停下 住手
Stop. Stop it.
我以我的性命起誓
I swear to you on my life.
我没有找到灵魂原石
I never found the Soul Stone.
读取记忆档案
Accessing memory files.
你知道他打算做什么
You know what he's about to do.
现在他终于准备好了 他要去掠夺原石了
He's finally ready, and he's going for the stones.
-全部原石 -他不可能得到全部的原石
- All of them. - He can never get them all.
他会的
He will!
他不会的 星云
He can't, Nebula.
因为我找到了通往灵魂原石的地图
Because I found the map to the Soul Stone...
然后我把它烧成了灰 我烧掉了
and I burned it to ash. I burned it.
你的坚强
You're strong.
是我教的
Me.
你的慷慨
You're generous.
也是我教的
Me.
但我从未教过你说谎
But I never taught you to lie.
难怪你撒谎如此拙劣
That's why you're so bad at it.
灵魂原石在哪里
Where is the Soul Stone?
沃米尔星
Vormir!
灵魂原石在沃米尔星
The stone is on Vormir.
带路
Show me.
我是格鲁特
I am Groot.
尿在杯子里
Tinkle in the cup.
我们不看 有什么好看的
We're not looking. What's there to see?
害羞什么 谁没见过小树枝
What's a twig? Everybody's seen a twig before.
我是格鲁特
I am Groot.
小树 把杯子里的东西倒进太空
Tree, pour what's in the cup
再继续尿在里面
out into space and go in the cup again.
你会说格鲁特语
You speak Groot?
嗯 我在阿斯加德选修过
Yes, they taught it on Asgard. It was an elective.
我是格鲁特
I am Groot.
我们快到的时候你就知道了
You'll know when we're close.
尼德威阿尔的熔炉
Nidavellir's forge harnesses
能收集中子星喷发的能量
the blazing power of a neutron star.
我的锤子就是在那里铸造的
It's the birthplace of my hammer.
它的力量十分惊人
It's truly awesome.
好吧 是时候尽船长的职责了
Okay, time to be the captain.
你弟弟死了 是吗
So, dead brother, huh?
那确实挺伤感的
Yeah, that could be annoying.
嗯 他以前也死过
Well, he's been dead before.
但是我觉得这次可能是真的了
But, no, this time I think it really might be true.
你还提到过你姐姐和爸爸
And you said your sister and your dad?
都死了
Both dead.
那至少还有个妈妈是吧
But still got a mom, though?
被一个黑暗精灵杀了
Killed by a dark elf.
最好的朋友呢
A best friend?
心脏被刺穿
Stabbed through the heart.
你确定你要参加这次特别的刺杀行动吗
You sure you're up to this particular murder mission?
当然
Absolutely.
怒火 复仇 愤怒 失落 悔恨
Rage and vengeance, anger, loss, regret...
都是我的动力
they're all tremendous motivators.
它们能让我保持头脑清醒
They really clear the mind.
所以我准备好了
So I'm good to go.
没错 但我们说的可是灭霸
Yeah, but this Thanos we're talkin' about...
他是最难对付的
he's the toughest there is.
-那是他没有跟我打过 -他有
- Well, he's never fought me. - Yeah, he has.
他没有跟我打过两次
He's never fought me twice.
还有别忘了 我要拿到新锤子了
And I'm getting a new hammer, don't forget.
那锤子最好厉害一点
It better be some hammer.
我已经1500岁了
You know, I'm 1,500 years old.
我杀过两倍于这个数字的敌人
I've killed twice as many enemies as that.
他们每一个都想置我于死地
And every one of them would've rather killed me,
却没一个成功
but none succeeded.
是命运要我活着
I'm only alive because fate wants me alive.
灭霸只是这些混蛋中的一个
Thanos is just the latest in a long line of bastards...
他也将尝到我复仇的怒火
and he'll be the latest to feel my vengeance.
这也是命运的安排
Fate wills it so.
那万一你错了呢
And what if you're wrong?
如果我错了 那
If I'm wrong, then...
我还有什么可失去的呢
what more could I lose?
我能失去的还有很多
I could lose a lot.
我在世上还有很多牵挂
Me, personally, I could lose a lot.
好吧
Okay.
如果命运真的想让你杀死那个王八蛋
If fate does want you to kill that crapsack...
你就不能只有一只眼睛
you're gonna need more than one stupid eyeball.
-这是什么 -这看起来像什么
- What's this? - What's it look like?
一个混球在康特阿克夏星打赌输给了我
Some jerk lost a bet with me on Contraxia.
他把眼睛给你了
He gave you his eye?
才不是 他给了我100个筹码
No, he gave me 100 credits.
我当晚溜进他的房间偷走了他的眼睛
I snuck into his room later that night and stole his eye.
谢谢 可爱的兔兔
Thank you, sweet rabbit.
嗯
Huh?
噢
Oh.
要是我的话就先洗一下
I would've washed that.
唯一能把它带出康特阿克夏星的方法就是把它塞到我的
The only way I could sneak it off Contraxia was up my...
嘿 我们到了
Hey, we're here!
我觉得这东西不管用
I don't think this thing works.
我的眼前一片漆黑
Everything seems dark.
不是眼睛的问题
It ain't the eye.
有哪里不对劲
Something's wrong.
这颗星球熄灭了
The star's gone out.
行星环也停住了
And the rings are frozen.
希望这些矮人
I hope these dwarves are better
铸造武器的手艺比他们打扫的本领强
at forging than they are cleaning.
或许他们搬家是因为意识到了
Maybe they realized that they live
他们住在宇宙的一个垃圾堆里
in a junk pile in the middle of space.
这座熔炉几个世纪以来都没有熄灭过
This forge hasn't gone dark in centuries.
你说过灭霸有个无限手套 是吗
You said Thanos had a gauntlet, right?
是的 怎么了
Yes, why?
它是长这样吗
It look anything like that?
我是格鲁特
I am Groot.
回分离舱上去
Go back to the pod.
伊特里 等等
Eitri, wait!
停下
Stop!
住手
Stop.
索尔
Thor?
这里发生了什么
What happened here?
你本应该保护我们的
You were supposed to protect us.
阿斯加德本应该保护我们的
Asgard was supposed to protect us.
阿斯加德被毁灭了
Asgard is destroyed.
伊特里 那个手套 你们做了什么
Eitri, the glove. What did you do?
有三百个矮人住在这个行星环上
300 dwarves lived on this ring.
我以为只要我按他的要求做了 他们就会安全
I thought if I did what he asked, they'd be safe.
我铸造了他想要的
I made what he wanted.
一个能够驾驭无限原石力量的装置
A device capable of harnessing the power of the stones.
然而 他还是杀了所有人
Then he killed everyone anyway.
除了我
All except me.
“你的生命属于你自己” 他说
"Your life is yours," He said.
“但你的双手属于我”
"But your hands are mine alone."
伊特里 这已经不仅仅是你手的问题了
Eitri, this isn't about your hands.
所有你所设计的武器
Every weapon you've ever designed,
每一个战斧 锤子 宝剑
every axe, hammer, sword...
全都刻在你的脑子里
it's all inside your head.
现在 我知道这一切看起来毫无希望
Now, I know it feels like all hope is lost.
相信我 我知道
Trust me, I know.
但是 你我一起 我们就能够杀掉灭霸
But together, you and I, we can kill Thanos.
曼蒂斯 仔细听我说
Mantis, listen very carefully.
我要你去泰坦星见我
I need you to meet me on Titan.
嘿 怎么了
Hey, what's going on?
我想我们到了
I think we're here.
我觉得这艘船大概没有自动降落功能
I don't think this rig has a self-park function.
把你的手放进操纵环架里
Get your hand inside the steering gimbal.
把这些关掉
Close those around it.
-你明白了吗 -明白了
- You understand? - Yep, got it.
这是一个大个子的操纵台 所以我们需要
This was meant for one big guy, so we gotta
-一起行动 -好的 准备好了
- move at the same time. - Okay, okay. Ready.
我们可能需要转向
We might wanna turn.
转向 转向 转向
Turn! Turn! Turn!
你还好吗
You all right?
好险
That was close.
我欠你一次
I owe you one.
我提前说一句
Let me just say, if aliens
如果异形在我胸腔里产了卵
wind up implanting eggs in my chest or something...
然后我吃了你们其中一个 那就抱歉了
and I eat one of you, I'm sorry.
在接下来的旅途中
I do not want another single pop culture reference
我都不想再听到你说任何流行文化的梗了 你明白了吗
out of you for the rest of the trip. You understand?
我想说的是 有什么东西过来了
I'm trying to say that something is coming.
灭霸
Thanos!
天哪 求你别在我身体里产卵
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Please don't put your eggs in me!
去死吧 小丑
Stay down, clown.
受死吧 死亡之毯
Die, blanket of death!
所有人待在原地 冷静一下
Everybody stay where you are. Chill the eff out.
我只问你一次
I'm gonna ask you this one time.
卡魔拉在哪里
Where is Gamora?
我问你一个更好的问题 卡魔拉是谁
Yeah. I'll do you one better. Who's Gamora?
我来问一个更好的问题 为什么要抓卡魔拉
I'll do you one better. Why is Gamora?
告诉我那女孩在哪里 不然我发誓
Tell me where the girl is or I swear to you
我会把这个小怪物炸成薯条
I'm gonna French fry this little freak.
谁怕谁 你给我的人一枪 我就给他一炮 来啊
Let's do it. You shoot my guy and I'll blast him. Let's go!
动手 奎尔 我能受得住
Do it, Quill! I can take it.
-不 他受不住的 -她说得对 你受不住
- No, he can't take it! - She's right. You can't.
哦 是吗 你不打算告诉我她在哪里是吗 没关系
Oh, yeah? You don't wanna tell me where she is? That's fine.
我会干掉你们三个
I'll kill all three of you
然后亲自去拷问灭霸
and I'll beat it out of Thanos myself.
就从你开始
Starting with you.
等等 等等 灭霸
Wait, what, Thanos?
好了 我就问你一遍
All right, let me ask you this one time.
你效忠于何人
What master do you serve?
我效忠于何人
What master do I serve?
我该怎么说 效忠于"耶稣"吗
What am I supposed to say, "Jesus"?
你是地球人
You're from Earth.
我才不是 我密苏里人
I'm not from Earth, I'm from Missouri.
密苏里就在地球上 蠢货
Yeah, that's on Earth, dipshit.
那你们为什么要找我们麻烦
What are you hassling us for?
所以你们不是和灭霸一伙的
So you're not with Thanos?
和灭霸一伙？
With Thanos?
才不是 我是来杀灭霸的
No, I'm here to kill Thanos.
他绑走了我女朋友 等等 你们到底是谁
He took my girl. Wait, who are you?
-我们是复仇者联盟 哥们儿 -哦
- We're the Avengers, man. - Oh.
你们就是索尔跟我们说的那些人
You're the ones Thor told us about.
你认识索尔
You know Thor?
对
Yeah.
高个子 长得不帅 心理还有问题
Tall guy, not that good-looking, needed saving.
他现在在哪里
Where is he now?
这就是计划吗 我们带着一块砖去拍他
This is the plan? We're gonna hit him with a brick?
这只是个模具
It's a mold.
王之武器
A king's weapon.
本是阿斯加德之最
Meant to be the greatest in Asgard.
理论上 它甚至可以召唤彩虹桥
In theory, it could even summon the Bifrost.
它有名字吗
Did it have a name?
风暴之锤
Stormbreaker.
有点中二
That's a bit much.
所以我们要怎么把它造出来
So how do we make it?
你要重新燃起熔炉
You'll have to restart the forge.
唤醒一颗濒死星球的心脏
Awaken the heart of a dying star.
兔子 去启动分离舱
Rabbit, fire up the pod.
这星球到底经历了什么
The hell happened to this planet?
偏离了轴线八度
It's eight degrees off its axis.
引力到处都是
Gravitational pull is all over the place.
是啊 我们有一个优势 他会来找我们的
Yeah, we got one advantage. He's coming to us.
我们就利用这点 好了 我有个计划
We'll use it. All right, I have a plan.
或者至少是初步计划
Or at least the beginnings of one.
很简单 我们把他引过来
It's pretty simple. We draw him in,
合力擒住他 拿走我们需要的
pin him down, get what we need.
我们明显不能和这家伙周旋纠缠
Definitely don't wanna dance with this guy.
我们只需要拿到手套
We just want the gauntlet.
你是在打哈欠吗
Are you yawning?
在我解释计划的这个时候 哈
In the middle of this, while I'm breaking it down? Huh?
你有听到我说了什么吗
Did you hear what I said?
在你说“我们需要一个计划”之后 我就没再听了
I stopped listening after you said, "We need a plan."
好吧 光头先生沉浸在自己的世界里
Okay, Mr. Clean is on his own page.
“别搞砸事情”不是他们的作风
See, "Not winging it" Isn't really what they do.
呃 那他们的实际作风是什么
Uh, what exactly is it that they do?
拉风头 抢仇恨
Kick names, take ass.
是的 没错
Yeah, that's right.
算了 先都聚过来吧 拜托了
All right, just get over here, please.
爵士先生 你能让你的人围过来吗
Mr. Lord, can you get your folks to circle up?
什么“爵士先生” 叫我星爵就行
"Mr. Lord." Star-Lord is fine.
我们要联合起来
We gotta coalesce.
因为如果我们全都迎面而上 是勇气可嘉的
'Cause if all we come at him with is a plucky attitude...
大哥 别跟我们说什么勇气
Dude, don't call us plucky.
我们不懂那是什么意思
We don't know what it means.
好吧 我们都很乐观 没错 我喜欢你的计划
All right, we're optimistic, yes. I like your plan.
不过它很烂 所以让我来定计划
Except it sucks, so let me do the plan...
这样我们的计划没准会很棒
and that way it might be really good.
告诉他你是怎么通过尬舞拯救宇宙的
Tell him about the dance-off to save the universe.
-什么尬舞 -没什么
- What dance-off? - It's nothing.
就像《浑身是劲》电影里那样吗
Like in Footloose, the movie?
没错 就跟《浑身是劲》一样
Exactly like Footloose.
它还是史上最棒的电影吗
Is it still the greatest movie in history?
它从来就不是
It never was.
别让他来劲 好吗
Don't encourage this, all right?
-好吧 -这位飞侠哥顿
- Okay. - We're getting no help
-显然帮不上我们什么 -飞侠哥顿
- from Flash Gordon here. - Flash Gordon?
顺便一说 那可是称赞
By the way, that's a compliment.
别忘了 我是半个人类
Don't forget, I'm half human.
所以那一半的我是蠢的
So that 50% of me that's stupid...
而你们就是百分百的蠢
that's 100% you.
你的数学真令我震惊
Your math is blowing my mind.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
但你们的朋友经常那样吗
But does your friend often do that?
斯特兰奇 你还好吗
Strange, we all right?
你回来了 你没事
You're back. You're all right.
-嗨 -嘿 刚刚是怎么回事
- Hi. - Hey, what was that?
我顺着时间前进 去浏览未来的可能
I went forward in time to view alternate futures.
去看即将来临的大战
To see all the possible outcomes
所有可能发生的结局
of the coming conflict.
你看到了多少种结局
How many did you see?
一千四百万六百零五种
14,000,605.
我们赢了多少次
How many did we win?
一次
One.
为了你妹妹小命
The stone had better be up there.
原石最好在那里
For your sister's sake.
欢迎 灭霸 阿拉尔斯之子
Welcome, Thanos, son of Alars.
卡魔拉 灭霸之女
Gamora, daughter of Thanos.
你认识我们
You know us?
认识每一个来到这里的人就是我的诅咒
It is my curse to know all who journey here.
灵魂原石在哪里
Where is the Soul Stone?
你该知道
You should know...
它会让你付出可怕的代价
it extracts a terrible price.
我准备好了
I am prepared.
一开始 我们都这样以为
We all think that at first.
但我们都错了
We are all wrong.
你为什么对这个地方如此熟悉
How is it you know this place so well?
一百年前 我也试图寻找无限原石
A lifetime ago, I, too, sought the stones.
甚至已经有一颗在我的手上
I even held one in my hand.
但它驱逐了我 将我流放至此
But it cast me out, banished me here.
指引他人搜寻我无法拥有的珍宝
Guiding others to a treasure I cannot possess.
你所寻找的就在你面前
What you seek lies in front of you.
你所畏惧的也是如此
As does what you fear.
这是什么
What's this?
代价
The price.
在所有无限原石中 灵魂原石有着特殊的地位
Soul holds a special place among the Infinity Stones.
可以说 它有一定的智慧
You might say it has a certain wisdom.
告诉我 它需要什么
Tell me what it needs.
为了确保拥有它的人
To ensure that whoever possesses it...
理解它的能量
understands its power...
这颗原石需要献祭
the stone demands a sacrifice.
献祭什么
Of what?
为了获得灵魂原石
In order to take the stone,
你必须失去你所爱的
you must lose that which you love.
一个灵魂
A soul...
换取另一个灵魂
for a soul.
我这一生 都梦想着有一天
All my life, I dreamed of a day...
有一个时刻
a moment...
你会遭到报应
when you got what you deserved.
但我总会失望
And I was always so disappointed.
但是现在
But now...
你杀戮 折磨他人
You kill and torture...
还称之为仁慈
and you call it mercy.
宇宙给了你判决
The universe has judged you.
你想让它给你奖赏 而它对你说不
You asked it for a prize, and it told you no.
你失败了
You failed.
你想知道为什么吗
And do you wanna know why?
因为你什么都不爱
Because you love nothing.
谁都不爱
No one.
不对
No.
真的吗
Really?
哭了
Tears?
这眼泪不是为他自己而流
They're not for him.
不
No.
这不是爱
This isn't love.
我曾忽视过自己的命运
I ignored my destiny once.
我不能重蹈覆辙
I cannot do that again.
即使是为了你
Even for you.
我很抱歉 小家伙
I'm sorry, little one.
不
No!
降低高度到2600 朝0-3-0坐标前进
Drop to 2600, heading 0-3-0.
我希望你没搞错
I hope you're right about this.
不然我们可就提前着陆了
Or we're gonna land a lot faster than you want to.
当你说我们要向世界
When you said we were going to open Wakanda
开放瓦坎达的时候
to the rest of the world...
我可没想到是这样子的
this is not what I imagined.
你以为是什么样子
And what did you imagine?
参加奥林匹克运动会
The Olympics.
或许再开个星巴克
Maybe even a Starbucks.
我们该行礼吗
Should we bow?
当然了 他可是国王
Yeah, he's a king.
似乎我总是在向你道谢
Seems like I'm always thanking you for something.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我们这里不用行礼
Uh, we don't do that here.
所以 我们会面临多大规模的战斗
So how big of an assault should we expect?
呃 陛下 我想你们要做好准备应对一场激烈的战斗
Uh, sir, I think you should expect quite a big assault.
我们有多少兵力
How we looking?
我们这边出战的有我的国王护卫队
You will have my Kingsguard,
边境部落 女子皇家亲卫队 还有
the Border Tribe, the Dora Milaje, and...
还有一位处于半稳定状态的百岁老人
And a semi-stable 100-year-old man.
你怎么样 巴基
How you been, Buck?
还行吧 毕竟世界末日都要来了
Uh, not bad, for the end of the world.
哇
Whoa.
原石是多形态结构的水晶
The structure is polymorphic.
没错 我们必须对每个神经元进行非序列性连接
Right, we had to attach each neuron non-sequentially.
你们为什么不对神经元突触
Why didn't you just reprogram
进行重新编码 使其能协调地工作
the synapses to work collectively?
因为我们没想到这一点
Because we didn't think of it.
我相信你们已经尽力了
I'm sure you did your best.
你能做到吗
Can you do it?
能 但这里有超过两万亿的神经元
Yes, but there are more than two trillion neurons here.
一点偏差就会导致一连串的回路故障
One misalignment could cause a cascade of circuit failures.
我需要时间 哥哥
It will take time, brother.
多长时间
How long?
越长越好
As long as you can give me.
有外来物正在侵入大气层
Something's entered the atmosphere.
队长 我们这里有情况
Hey, Cap, we got a situation here.
天呐 我爱死这个地方了
God, I love this place.
先别急着欢呼 伙计们
Yeah, don't start celebrating yet, guys.
穹顶外有更多的攻击要来了
We got more incoming outside the dome.
太迟了
It's too late.
我们必须现在就毁掉原石
We need to destroy the stone now.
幻视 乖乖躺回桌上
Vision, get your ass back on the table.
我们会拖住他们的
We will hold them off.
旺达 一旦原石离开了他的头
Wanda, as soon as that stone's out of his head...
你就立刻毁了它
you blow it to hell.
我会的
I will.
疏散全城 全面戒备
Evacuate the city. Engage all defenses.
给这个男人一块盾牌
And get this man a shield.
我觉得
I don't think
你不懂这里的科学系统如何运作
you get the scientifics here.
这些行星环庞大无比 想让它们动起来
These rings are gigantic. You wanna get them moving...
你需要更大的东西
you're gonna need something a lot bigger
才能拉动它们
to yank 'em loose.
-交给我 -交给你
- Leave that to me. - Leave it to you?
哥们 你是在太空里 你手里只有一条绳子和一个
Buddy, you're in space. All you got is a rope and a...
发动引擎
Fire the engines!
加大火力 兔子
More power, rabbit!
干得好 孩子
Well done, boy.
这才是尼德威阿尔
That's Nidavellir.
该死
Damn it.
“该死” “该死”是什么意思
"Damn it"? What's "Damn it"?
机械装置出故障了
The mechanism is crippled.
-什么 -光圈闭合的话
- What? - With the iris closed,
我就没办法加热金属
I can't heat the metal.
加热需要多长时间
How long will it take to heat it?
几分钟 或者更久 为什么这么问
A few minutes, maybe more. Why?
我去撑开它
I'm gonna hold it open.
你这是在自杀
That's suicide.
不带那把斧子去迎战灭霸也是自杀
So is facing Thanos without that axe.
你感觉怎么样 布鲁斯
How we looking, Bruce?
挺好 我觉得我开始适应了
Yeah, I think I'm getting the hang of it.
哇 太炫了 大家伙儿
Wow! This is amazing, man.
感觉就像不用变身就成了浩克
It's like being the Hulk without actually...
我没事 我没事
I'm okay. I'm okay.
我发现有两个热信号
I've got two heat signatures
正在突破林木线
breaking through the tree line.
感谢你们能与我们并肩作战
Thank you for standing with us.
你的另一个丑朋友呢
Where's your other friend?
你们会为他偿命的
You will pay for his life with yours.
灭霸将会拿到那颗原石
Thanos will have that stone.
想都别想
That's not gonna happen.
你们现在是在瓦坎达
You are in Wakanda now.
灭霸只会得到灰烬和鲜血
Thanos will have nothing but dust and blood.
我们的血多得是
We have blood to spare.
他们投降了吗
They surrender?
没有
Not exactly.
什么鬼东西
What the hell?
看来我们惹毛她了
Looks like we pissed her off.
他们是在自杀
They're killing themselves.
你看到那些怪物的牙了吗
You see the teeth on those things?
好了 退后 山姆
All right, back up, Sam.
你会烤焦你的翅膀的
You're gonna get your wings singed.
队长 如果这些怪物绕过防护线
Cap, if these things circle the perimeter
从我们后面攻进来
and get in behind us...
那可就直接扑上幻视了
there's nothing between them and Vision.
那么我们最好把他们牵制在我们跟前
Then we better keep 'em in front of us.
我们该怎么做
How do we do that?
我们打开屏障
We open the barrier.
听我的指令 打开西北部第十七号屏障
On my signal, open North-West Section Seventeen.
请确认指令 陛下
Requesting confirmation, My King.
您刚刚是说打开屏障吗
You said open the barrier?
听我的指令
On my signal.
这会是瓦坎达的末日
This will be the end of Wakanda.
那这也将是史上最辉煌的落幕
Then it will be the noblest ending in history.
瓦坎达万岁
Wakanda forever!
就现在
Now!
还要多久 苏睿
How much longer, Shuri?
我才刚刚开始 哥哥
I've barely begun, brother.
你最好加快速度
You might want to pick up the pace.
天父啊 请赐予我力量
Allfathers, give me strength.
你明白吗 孩子
You understand, boy?
你将会承受一颗星球的全部力量
You're about to take the full force of a star.
你会死的
It'll kill you.
真死了再说
Only if I die.
没错
Yes.
这就是“死”的意思
That's what killing you means.
坚持 坚持住 索尔
Hold it! Hold it, Thor!
索尔 说句话 拜托
Thor! Say something. Come on.
索尔 你还好吗
Thor, you okay?
我觉得他快死了
I think he's dying.
他需要这把斧头
He needs the axe!
斧柄在哪里
Where's the handle?
树人 快帮我找找斧柄
Tree, help me find the handle!
它们的数量太多了
There's too many of 'em!
你们要大祸临头了
You guys are so screwed now!
给我把灭霸叫来
Bring me Thanos!
啊 没错
Oh, yeah.
灭霸人如其名
You're much more of a Thanos.
看来乌木喉已经死了
I take it the Maw is dead.
今天伤亡惨重
This day extracts a heavy toll.
不过 他还是完成了他的任务
Still, he accomplished his mission.
你会后悔的
You may regret that.
他让你和至尊法师
He brought you face-to-face
正面对决
with the Master of the Mystic Arts.
你认为他把你带到了哪儿
And where do you think he brought you?
让我猜猜 你的家乡吗
Let me guess. Your home?
曾经是
It was.
过去它是那么的美
And it was beautiful.
泰坦像许多其他的星球那样
Titan was like most planets.
人口太多 资源却不够
Too many mouths, not enough to go around.
当我们面临灭绝的时候 我提出了一个解决办法
And when we faced extinction, I offered a solution.
大屠杀
Genocide.
随机 公正 无论贫富贵贱
But random, dispassionate, fair to rich and poor alike.
他们说我是疯子
They called me a madman.
但我所预言的最终却成真了
And what I predicted came to pass.
那恭喜你了 你可真是个预言家
Congratulations, you're a prophet.
我是个幸存者
I'm a survivor.
一个想杀死亿万人的幸存者
Who wants to murder trillions.
集齐六块原石 我只需要轻松地打个响指
With all six stones, I could simply snap my fingers.
他们就不复存在了 这是我的仁慈
They would all cease to exist. I call that mercy.
然后呢
And then what?
我才能最终得到安歇
I'd finally rest...
看着太阳在一个对我充满感激的宇宙里升起
and watch the sun rise on a grateful universe.
只有意志最坚强的人才能做出如此艰难的选择
The hardest choices require the strongest wills.
你马上就会知道我们的意志也跟你的一样强
I think you'll find our will equal to yours.
我们的
Our?
小菜一碟 奎尔
Piece of cake, Quill.
是啊 如果你只是想惹毛他的话
Yeah, if your goal was to piss him off.
嘣
Boom!
不要让他合上拳头
Don't let him close his fist.
看我的魔法
Magic.
更多魔法
More magic.
魔法加一个飞踢
Magic with a kick.
魔法加一个
Magic with a...
臭虫子
Insect!
原来是你
Well, well.
你早该杀了我的
You should've killed me.
那可就浪费了你身上的零件了
It would've been a waste of parts!
卡魔拉在哪
Where's Gamora?
控制住他了吗 不要放松
Is he under? Don't let up.
快一点 他太强壮了
Be quick. He is very strong.
帕克 快来这儿帮忙
Parker, help! Get over here.
她坚持不了多久 快动手
She can't hold him much longer. Let's go.
我们得掰开他的手指才能拿下来
We gotta open his fingers to get it off.
我还以为你很难对付呢
I thought you'd be hard to catch.
以防大家不知道 这是我的计划
For the record, this was my plan.
现在没那么嚣张了吧
You're not so strong now, huh?
卡魔拉在哪
Where is Gamora?
是我的卡魔拉
My Gamora.
你放屁
No, bullshit!
她在哪
Where is she?
他现在极度痛苦
He is in anguish.
很好
Good.
他 他在哀悼
He... He mourns.
这个怪物有什么好哀悼的
What does this monster have to mourn?
卡魔拉
Gamora.
什么
What?
他带她去了沃米尔星
He took her to Vormir.
然后他带着灵魂原石回来了
He came back with the Soul Stone.
她却没回来
But she didn't.
奎尔 你现在得冷静下来 你明白吗
Okay, Quill, you gotta cool it right now. You understand?
别别别 别动手 我们马上就要摘下来了
Don't, don't. Don't engage. We almost got this off!
告诉我她在撒谎
Tell me she's lying.
混蛋 告诉我你没杀她
Asshole, tell me you didn't do it!
我必须那么做
I had to.
不 你没有
No, you didn't.
-不 你没有杀她 -奎尔
- No, you didn't! - Quill!
嘿 住手 住手 住手
Hey, stop! Hey, stop! Stop!
住手 住手
Hey, stop! Stop!
快掉了 快掉了 我摘下来了 我摘下来了
It's coming, it's coming. I got it, I got it!
不 天呐
Oh, God.
来尝尝我的子弹吧 太空狗
Come and get some, space dogs!
来呀 尝尝我的厉害
Come on! Get some! Get some!
来呀 来打呀
Come on! Get some!
-你的枪多少钱 -不卖
- How much for the gun? - Not for sale.
好吧 那手臂多少钱
Okay. How much for the arm?
行吧 我会自己搞到手的
Oh, I'll get that arm.
新发型吗
New haircut?
你留的那胡子是学我的吧
Noticed you've copied my beard.
顺便说下 这是我朋友 小树
By the way, this is a friend of mine, Tree.
我是格鲁特
I am Groot.
我是史蒂夫·罗杰斯
I am Steve Rogers.
撤退 撤退 快
Fall back! Fall back, now!
山姆 瞄准左翼开火
Focus that fire on the left flank, Sam.
正在这么做
I'm doing it.
她怎么不早点下来帮忙
Why was she up there all this time?
引她出来了 去抢原石吧
She's on the field. Take it.
伙伴们 幻视那边有危险了
Guys, we got a Vision situation here.
快去幻视那边
Somebody get to Vision!
-我去帮他 -我马上到
- I got him! - On my way.
他会孤独地死去 你也是
He'll die alone. As will you.
她可没有落单
She's not alone.
住手 你们休想
Oh, no, you don't.
这次可不会像在纽约时一样 伙计
This isn't gonna be like New York, pal.
这套装甲曾经可是把浩克都揍扁过
This suit's already kicked the crap outta the Hulk.
什么 不 不要
What? No! No!
伙计们 幻视现在需要支援
Guys! Vision needs backup, now!
浩克 浩克
Hulk? Hulk,
我知道你喜欢在最后关头出场
I know you like making your entrance at the last second.
现在就是了 哥们 现在就是最后关头
Well, this is it, man. This is the last, last second.
浩克 浩克
Hulk! Hulk!
浩克
Hulk!
我不
No!
去你的 你这个绿色大饭桶
Oh, screw you, you big, green asshole!
我自己上
I'll do it myself!
来呀
Come on! Yeah!
拜拜咯
See ya!
浩克 我们得好好谈谈了
Hulk, we got a lot to figure out, pal.
我还以为你有多厉害呢 机器人
I thought you were formidable, machine.
但你却要死了 像所有凡人一样
But you're dying, like any man.
快离开这里
Get outta here!
快走
Go!
真恶心
That was really gross.
我不是叫你走了吗
I thought I told you to go.
我们从不以命换命 这是队长你说的
We don't trade lives, Captain.
我接住你了 我接住你了
I got you. I got you.
不好意思我记不住大家的名字
I'm sorry I can't remember anybody's names.
你的花样还真多 巫师
You're full of tricks, wizard.
但你却一次也没用过你最强大的武器
Yet you never once used your greatest weapon.
假的
A fake.
你要是再拿月球砸我 我就要发狂了
You throw another moon at me, and I'm gonna lose it.
史塔克
Stark.
你认识我
You know me?
当然认识
I do.
你可不是唯一一个被知识诅咒的人
You're not the only one cursed with knowledge.
我唯一的诅咒就是你
My only curse is you.
来吧
Come on!
忙活那么久就为了让我出点血
All that for a drop of blood.
你赢得了我的尊敬 史塔克
You have my respect, Stark.
等我成功后 一半的人类还会活着
When I'm done, half of humanity will still be alive.
我希望他们会记得你
I hope they remember you.
住手
Stop.
放他一条生路
Spare his life...
我就把原石交给你
and I will give you the stone.
别耍花招
No tricks.
不要
Don't.
还剩一颗
One to go.
他去哪儿了
Where is he?
我们输了吗
Did we just lose?
你为什么要那么做
Why would you do that?
我们已经没戏唱了
We're in the endgame now.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
怎么了 怎么回事
What? What is it?
他来了
He's here.
所有人注意 我的位置 有敌人来袭
Everyone, on my position. We have incoming.
什么鬼
What the hell?
队长
Cap.
就是他
That's him.
全体集中注意 保持警惕
Eyes up. Stay sharp.
旺达
Wanda.
是时候了
It's time.
不
No.
他们阻止不了他 旺达 但我们可以
They can't stop him, Wanda, but we can.
看着我
Look at me.
你有能力摧毁原石
You have the power to destroy the stone.
不行
Don't.
你必须得这么做 旺达 求你了
You must do it. Wanda, please.
我们已经没有时间了
We are out of time.
我做不到
I can't.
不 你可以的
Yes, you can.
你能做到
You can.
如果他得到了原石 宇宙中一半的人都会死
If he gets the stone, half the universe dies.
这不公平
It's not fair.
这不该由你来做 但只能如此
It shouldn't be you, but it is.
没关系的
It's all right.
你不会伤害到我的
You could never hurt me.
我感受到你了
I just feel you.
没事的
It's all right.
没关系的
我爱你
I love you.
我明白你的感受 我的孩子
I understand, my child.
比任何人都明白
Better than anyone.
你永远也不会懂
You could never.
我今天所失去的远比你想象的还要多
Today, I lost more than you can know.
但我现在没有时间去哀悼
But now is no time to mourn.
现在没有时间
Now is no time at all.
不
No!
我告诉过你
I told you...
你会偿命的
you'd die for that.
你应该
You should have...
You should...
你应该朝着我的头砍
You should have gone for the head.
不
No!
女儿
Daughter?
你做到了吗
Did you do it?
是的
Yes.
代价是什么
What did it cost?
我的一切
Everything.
你做了什么
What did you do?
你刚刚做了什么
What'd you do?
他去哪儿了
Where'd he go?
索尔
Thor.
他去哪了
Where'd he go?
史蒂夫
Steve?
起来 将军 起来
Up, General. Up!
我们不能死在这里
This is no place to die.
我是格鲁特
I am Groot.
噢
Oh...
不 不 不
No, no, no!
格鲁特 不要
Groot! No.
山姆
Sam!
山姆 你在哪儿
Sam, where you at?
情况有些不对
Something's happening.
奎尔
Quill?
冷静 奎尔
Steady, Quill.
不是吧
Oh, man.
托尼
Tony.
没有其他办法了
There was no other way.
史塔克先生
Mr. Stark?
我不太舒服
I don't feel so good.
你会没事的
You're all right.
我不 我不知道怎么回事
I don't... I don't know what's happening.
我不知道
I don't know...
我不想消失
I don't want to go.
先生 我不想消失 求你了
I don't want to go, sir. Please.
求求你 我不想消失 我不想
Please, I don't want to go. I don't want to go.
对不起
I'm sorry.
他做到了
He did it.
怎么回事 到底他妈的发生了什么
What is this? What the hell is happening?
天呐
Oh, God.
史塔克那里还没有消息吗
Still no word from Stark?
没 还没有
No, not yet.
我们监控着全球的所有卫星
We're watching every satellite
还是没有回应
on both hemispheres, but still nothing.
怎么了
What is it?
很多不明飞行物出现在瓦坎达
Multiple bogeys over Wakanda.
和纽约的怪物能量标志一样吗
Same energy signature as New York?
还要强上十倍
Ten times bigger.
告诉克莱恩我们和他在
Tell Klein we'll meet him at...
尼克 尼克
Nick! Nick!
他们没事吧
They okay?
里面没有人
There's no one here.
快呼叫控制中心
Call Control.
红色警报
Code red.
尼克
Nick.
希尔
Hill.
不是吧
Oh, no.
狗日
Mother...